auriq.com 2005-12-30

# Privacy Statement - AuriQ, Systems, Inc.

Home > Privacy Statement

**Your privacy matters to us.**  
AuriQ Systems envisions the Internet as a safe place where people can exchange ideas and information. We believe that safety on the Internet is a right and not a privilege.

AuriQ Systems, Inc. is dedicated to protecting the privacy of online users and follows the guidelines set forth by the Internet Advertising Bureau (IAB). This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for AuriQ Systems, Inc. and is designed to protect information that can be associated with an individual (Personal Identifiable Information) in an online environment.

**Our Website**  
AuriQ Systems is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. AuriQ uses information gathered from our website for the following general purposes: to customize the content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. AuriQ may collect information from our users when they choose to register or order on our website. During registration or ordering, a user may be required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. A user just browsing through our website never surrenders any direct demographical information. Although a user’s IP address can be traced when surfing, IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**A Note on Cookies**  
A "cookie" is a small text file that a website can place on your computer's hard drive in order, for example, to collect information about your activities on the site or to make it possible for you to use an online "shopping cart" to keep track of items you wish to purchase. The cookie transmits this information back to the Web site's computer which, generally speaking, is the only computer that can read it. Most consumers do not know that "cookies" are being placed on their computers when they visit websites. If you want to know when this happens, or to prevent it from happening, you can set your browser to warn you when a website attempts to place a "cookie" on your computer. AuriQ may set and access AuriQ cookies on your computer.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
AuriQ reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion, and will provide notice of material changes on the homepage of the Site.

**AuriQ Partners**  
This AuriQ Site may contain links to other company sites. We have no control nor are we responsible for the terms and privacy of these sites.

**Feedback**  
For any questions and concerns: <http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/index.html>

**Contact us:**  
US Toll Free Phone: 800.474.7188  
Questions regarding privacy: [privacy@auriq.com](mailto:privacy@auriq.com)  
General inquiries: [info@auriq.com](mailto:info@auriq.com)
